<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Mysore Tourism App</string>
    <string name="category_places">Places to visit</string>
    <string name="category_eat">Top restaurents</string>
    <string name="category_Stay">Best hotels</string>
    <string name="category_shop">Best places to shop</string>
    <string name="place1">Mysore Palace</string>
    <string name="place2">Chamundi Hill</string>
    <string name="place3">Mysore Zoo</string>
    <string name="place4">Mausoleum of Tipu Sultan</string>
    <string name="place5">Krishna Raja Sagara Dam</string>
    <string name="place6">Bird Santuary</string>
    <string name="place7">Bandipur National Park</string>
    <string name="pdesc1"> It is the official residence and seat of the Wodeyars — the rulers of Mysore, the royal family of Mysore.</string>
    <string name="pdesc2">Chamundeshwari Temple is a Hindu temple located on the top of Chamundi Hills.</string>
    <string name="pdesc3">Mysore Zoo is a 157-acre zoo located near the palace in Mysore, India. It is one of the oldest and most popular zoos in India.</string>
    <string name="pdesc4">Tipu Sultan, also known as the Tiger of Mysore, and Tipu Sahib, was a ruler of the Kingdom of Mysore.</string>
    <string name="pdesc5">KRS, is the name of both a lake and the dam that creates it. It is located close to the settlement of Krishnarajasagara.</string>
    <string name="pdesc6">Ranganathittu Bird Sanctuary also known as, the isles formed an important nesting ground for birds, and persuaded the Wodeyar kings of Mysore to declare the area a wildlife sanctuary in 1940.</string>
    <string name="pdesc7">Bandipur National Park, an 874-sq.-km forested reserve in the southern Indian state of Karnataka, is known for its small population of tigers.</string>
    <string name="E1">Oyster Bay</string>
    <string name="E2">Infinit Lounge Bar Fine Dining</string>
    <string name="E3">Green Leaf</string>
    <string name="E4">Poojaris Fish Land</string>
    <string name="E5">Barbeque Nation</string>
    <string name="E6">Kamat Madhuvan - Vegetarian</string>
    <string name="Edesc1"> Kannada Parishath Road, Vijayanagar 1st Stage, Mysuru, Karnataka 570017</string>
    <string name="Edesc2">Global dishes, cocktails and beer offered in contemporary surrounds with a rooftop terrace. Address: 2724/C, Bangalore Nilgiri Rd, Lashkar Mohalla, Doora, Mysuru, Karnataka 570001, India</string>
    <string name="Edesc3">12th Cross, Near ICICI Bank, Kalidasa Road, Vani Vilas Mohalla, Mysuru, Karnataka 570002, India</string>
    <string name="Edesc4">Mysore Bangalore Road, State Highway 17, Opp White, Kalasthavadi, Karnataka 570003, India.</string>
    <string name="Edesc5">Ground Floor, BM Habitat Mall,, Mangalore - Mysore Highway, Jayalakshmipuram, Mysuru, Karnataka 570012, India</string>
    <string name="Edesc6">#151, F2/1E, Khille Mohalla, Mysore Ooty Road, Mysuru, Karnataka 570010, India</string>
    <string name="Shop1">Mall of Mysore</string>
    <string name="Shop2">Devaraja Urs Market</string>
    <string name="Shop3">Government Sandalwood Oil Factory</string>
    <string name="Shop4">Karnataka Govt. Silk Factory</string>
    <string name="Shop5">Badsha Stores - The Silk Experience</string>
    <string name="Shop6">The Heritage</string>
    <string name="Sdesc1">Near Malabar Gold and Diamonds B.N.Road, Mysuru, Karnataka 570001, India</string>
    <string name="Sdesc2">No.C-1, M.G. Road, Indira Nagar Extension, Nazarbad Mohalla, Opposite Race Course, Near Mysore Zoo, Mysuru, Karnataka 570010</string>
    <string name="Sdesc3">Sayyaji Rao Rd, Devaraja Mohalla, Shivarampet, Mysuru, Karnataka 570001, India.</string>
    <string name="Sdesc4">Kuvempu Nagar 2nd Stage, Ashokapuram, Mysuru, Karnataka 570008, India.</string>
    <string name="Sdesc5">Vishveshwariah Bhavan,Manadavadi Road,K.R.Circle, Ashokapuram, Mysuru, Karnataka 570008.</string>
    <string name="Sdesc6">Shop# 5, Vishveshwarya Bhawan, KR Circle, Mysuru, Karnataka 570001, India.</string>
    <string name="Stay1">Sunflower Hotel</string>
    <string name="Stay2">Radisson Blu Plaza</string>
    <string name="Stay3">Ginger Hotel</string>
    <string name="Stay4">Hotel Pai Vista</string>
    <string name="Stay5">Fortune JP Palace</string>
    <string name="Stay6">Country Inn and Suites </string>
    <string name="StDesc1"># 331/A, Loyal World Centre, Bangalore - Mysore Road, Adjacent to St. Joseph Hospital, Bannimantap, Mysuru, Karnataka 570015, India</string>
    <string name="StDesc2">1, MG Road, Mysuru, Karnataka 570010, India</string>
    <string name="StDesc3">Nazarabad Mohalla, Near Nazarabad Police Station, Vasant Mahal Road, Opp Vasant Mahal, Mysuru, Karnataka 570010, India.</string>
    <string name="StDesc4"> 35/A, Behind Bhima Jewellery, Bangalore Nilgiri Road, Doora, Mysuru, Karnataka 570001, India.</string>
    <string name="StDesc5">#3, Abba Road, Nazarbad, Mysuru, Karnataka 570007, India.</string>
    <string name="StDesc6">Plot No. 345/A, Hebbal Industrial Area, Near Infosys Campus, Mysuru, Karnataka 570016, India.</string>

   </resources>
